SpaceX acquiring a low band frequency.
What the he double hockey sticks DOES
THAT EVEN MEAN? WHY DO WE FREAKING CARE?
I'll tell you why we care. It's because
the legacy mobile companies are shaking
in their freaking boots, baby. And there
are some of them that have actually
partnered with SpaceX. The first thing
you got to know, and this is not
sponsored by like any of these companies
that I'm about to mention, okay?
Although I do have exposure to SpaceX
stock in many different ways, both post
IPO selloff exposure to SpaceX and and
that's up from where we are now to be
clear. Uh and and we've been pretty
transparent on the channel about what
our thoughts are on SpaceX, right? We
IPOed. We had warnings about be careful
buying this after IPO has a shot of
memeing and then pulling back bigly.
That's what it did. We thought it was
going to go down 30% after IPO from like
IPO price. It went down about 32% I want
to say. Obviously way more if you count
from the top to the bottom. Since then,
fundamentals have substantially improved
for SpaceX. I personally think a floor
for the company is around 132. If you
could buy it around 132, I'm actually
bullish on SpaceX. I want to be clear
about that. These get the little
comments from the people who don't pay
attention all the time. But that's okay.
Everybody's got to have a little weeny
baby moment behind the freaking
keyboard. Come say it to my face.
Anyway, where were we? Oh, yes.
T-Mobile. All right. So, a company like
T-Mobile. I like T-Mobile, but I know
they rip me off. And please don't sue
me, bro. T-Mobile. This is a half
compliment and half ripoff alert. Okay.
Number one, T-Mobile
basically gives their cheap cheap stuff
that is basically just as fast to
another provider under a different
brand. I will explain in just a moment
how that works, but I don't want to
confuse that. But I'm going to tell you
what that brand is and actually might
save you a lot of money. And this, I'm
telling you, it sounds like an ad. And
they they actually reached out about
doing a sponsorship on the channel was
and then I ignored them. Maybe I
shouldn't have, but I'm not sponsored by
them. But this is going to explain
what's going on with this this banned
low band stuff. So T-Mobile basically
has this tendency of for their fancy
bull crap magenta plans or whatever
charging somewhere around $140 per
month. You know, you might pay 80. It
just depends on how much data you want.
I pay about $140 per month. I have five
different cellular services. Now don't
be like me. I'm a YouTuber and so I
can't get stuck somewhere without
service. So I have on this phone I have
two active at a time. Right now, I've
got uh T-Mobile, AT&T, Verizon, Mint,
and then I have uh the Google line,
which I actually also think is T-Mobile,
but I'm not sure about that because
there's no option to get Sprint anymore.
But anyway, I have them all basically. I
will be point blank about this. Verizon
is or sorry, uh T-Mobile is the absolute
best, like the least dead spots and the
fastest service that I have ever seen
anywhere. The problem is you're paying
140 bucks and most people don't need
unlimited data. So T-Mobile knows this.
T-Mobile knows that they're going to
sell their premium product under the uh
$140 label. But then what they do, this
is sort of the public label. And then
it's like, oh, you want the discount
label? Okay, it'll be $60 for seniors or
it'll be $80 or this that or whatever.
Okay. Then they go around and sell the
same thing supposedly with lower
priorities. I don't believe that because
I have uploaded videos through this
other provider and gotten just as good
speeds as I do on T-Mobile because it's
the same freaking tower in the same
network. It's all the same. And you're
going to see how SpaceX gets involved
here in just a moment. Okay. through a
back channel. They basically say, "Hey,
let's get the schmucks that only want to
pay $15 a month and only want five
gigabytes of service." Okay, that
doesn't sound like a lot. I think you
could actually get more. It I don't know
if the pricing on this is correct. It
might be more, it might be less. There's
an unlimited one in there somewhere, I
think. But basically, the dirt cheap
tier. Okay, so like the sub $25 tier.
Okay, I have it. I use it right
alongside T-Mobile. And you know what
it's called? It's called Ryan Reynolds.
my my homeboy Ryan Reynolds Mint Mobile.
#not
sponsorship. I don't even think I have
an affero referral link. It doesn't
matter. The point is it's the same crap,
but if they sold a $15 tier, everyone
who was at 60 or 80 would go down to 15
and they'd be effed. T-Mobile would be
screwed, baby. They don't want to be
screwed. Some people want to be screwed.
Some people want to get their business
unscrewed and then they call Sydney
Sweeney. And then there's Elon Musk who
sees this as a corporate wedge deal.
Y'all know me, okay? My little startup
Reinvest. I'm a big fan of what we call
wedge deals. That's basically when I
could buy a house for, let's say,
$750,000. I know that's a lot for a
house. And I could put 100 grand into
it. I know that's a lot. And then it's a
hundred or it's a million50 property. So
I'm up 200 grand. I'm up 20%. I can
place a tenant in it, rent it out for
the long term. I get tax benefits. Boom.
Capitalism one-on-one. I take an empty
house that was a trashy fixer upper. I
provide a roof over somebody's head
heads and they get the flexibility of
being able to rent and move whenever
they want. Well, you know, obviously
within their lease terms. So I like
wedges in real estate. Elon sees this as
a wedge. This is the brilliance of Elon.
People don't understand this. He sees
that on a massive scale, there's an
opportunity to stick it to these
schmucks. And guess who knows it? Guess
who knows that Elon is coming for their
guts?
T-Mobile. So, guess who one of the first
schmucks was to partner with T-Mobile?
Well, SpaceX, I meant to say one of the
first schmucks to partner with SpaceX
was T-Mobile.
What a surprise.
Because they're all trying to do
everything they can to stay at the
frontier and suck the, you know, milk
that's available to be sucked from these
spreads on selling you the same crap
under a different brand. That's it. It's
no different than you buying Kirkland
salted nuts and loading up your mouth
with salty, oily nuts and buying the
Planters salty oily nuts. They're the
same nuts, oily, salty nuts in your
mouth. It's the same thing except one of
them you paid $18 a pound for and one of
them you paid $12.99 a pound for. That's
it. It's the same thing here. It's a
phone call. It's a text. It's data. it
goes to a tower. They'd rather make some
money taking it from mint than ra
dropping their prices and giving
everybody the benefit. This is called an
oligopolistic
monopoly. Okay, it's an oligopoly. Okay,
a few small companies have so much
control and then they partner with the
little guys to make sure they maintain
control. That's why T-Mobile, like the
snake in the grass, is trying to partner
with SpaceX.
SpaceX is really smart though because
Elon, okay, this guy, he's like he's
like 10, 15 years in the future.
Honestly, some of his ideas are like a
hundred years into the future. His ideas
are not wrong. His timing is just
warped. The guy lives in a time warped
reality. And somehow that delusion
actually creates badass products. So
like, hats off to the delusion. Like
damn, sometimes I wish I could have that
delusion, you know? Instead, I think
realistic things like I think you're
going to sign up for Reinvest One and
together we are going to replace the
Bloomberg terminal. We are going to make
a product that's so good that you pay
lifetime access to this. We're going to
get rid of lifetime access for it unless
you lock it in. You lock it in, you're
going to keep lifetime access. Let's be
clear about that. But you get the alpha
membership, the trade alerts, the
reinvest stocks, the terminal which
includes real estate via the homes AI,
the reinvest research, all the nine
courses, the course member livereams,
the agentic for consumers blueprint, the
re the business blueprint, all of it in
one product at reinvest one.com. If you
have questions, you could email us or if
you're a course member, I encourage you
to email us. Uh because if you're a
course member, we can true you up. We
could upgrade you to this so you could
also get the benefits. So, just email us
at staff@reinvestone.com.
But see, I have reasonable expectations
like, you know, bankrupting Bloomberg
because I hate their damn guts and I
think they're the scum of the earth. So,
I am one of those revenge is a dish
served cold best served cold people.
Anyway, so that's what we're building
here. You're welcome to join us in my
realistic quest. Now, back to delusions
and grandeur. So SpaceX, this is really
smart. SpaceX wants to acquire the low
band spectrum for mobile phones. What
the hell is low band? I hear about high
bandwidth memory and that sounds sexy. I
hear about like I don't know, high
sounds better than low, right? I don't
want to be low. I'd rather be high than
low, right? Come on, man. Nobody wants
to be low.
low band is to get through these damn
windows. You see these right there?
Three windows right there. Can't see
them cuz, you know, someone decided to
drywall right over them, but there are
three windows right there. How are you
going to get cellular service from low
Earth orbit through these walls?
You beam it down with lasers to cell
towers. And from those cell towers, you
go spectrum it out
over a low band that could penetrate
these walls and radiate your boy meet
Kevin. You know how much radiation is
probably going through my brain right
now? Probably more radiation than you
can find in Pickax Mountain.
That's saying something. So anyway, low
band is the type of frequency that can
get through all the freaking fiberglass
I shoved into this wall. talking about
fiberglass. If you want a discount on
glass today, use my affiliate code for
corning stock. I'm just kidding. I don't
have an affiliate for Corning stock, but
the puppy's down like 6.3% today. So,
you know, they're having a little sale
today. So is Bitcoin. Michael Sailor
Mekevin.com/BTC.
That doesn't exist. [laughter]
You could try it and see what happens.
You know what? Try it.
Uh but anyway, so uh the deal is to
enable SpaceX to use its Starlink
satellite service to become a major
mobile carrier in the US. They're trying
to do the wedge deals. And honestly, I
would love Elon to take over my phone
service. And Apple's already partnering
with them. See, Apple's smart. You know
why Apple is partnering with Elon? I
want you to think about that for a
moment. Apple wants to sell. Like, I
hate to say this, but if you're older or
you're retired or whatever, how often
are you updating your damn phone? I
don't know, once every four years, you
don't want to reinstall the apps. You
ain't got time for that cuz you're
retired. And even though you got all the
time in the world, you don't want to do
it. You know who upgrades to the new
damn device every year? It's those damn
like upper 20 and under 45year-old dudes
that are like, "No, bro. If if I could
be 15% faster, bro, I could buy another
meat Kevin course.
That's exactly like me. Okay, I'mma buy
the iPhone duel and then I'mma throw
this iPhone 17 out the window and then
maybe maybe this has been sitting on my
desk for like two weeks because I bought
the last Apple Watch Ultra because for
some reason I actually got sold to buy
Oh, there goes my heart rate again. 84.
Anyway, for some reason I decided to get
the new one and I still haven't traded
in the old one. People like me can keep
buying this crap. But you know what
would be the best sales pitch is getting
some Starlink onto this heart rate.
So, Apple has partnered with Starlink
for direct from space to phone service,
but then you got to sit out there like
this and it's kind of Like,
even in the mountains, it's like, "Oh, I
need a direct view, but I'm stuck in a
tree well and I'm under 2 ft of snow. I
could really use some satellite service
to call for help here. Oh, I can't cuz
I'm buried in the snow and I can't see
the satellites cuz I'm under all these
pine trees. This sucks. Wish I brought a
shovel. Oh, wait. I did bring a shovel.
It's right here in my backpack.
Anyway,
all right. So, obviously, this is a
brilliant move by uh by Elon Musk. And
the whole premise is how can we get to
consumers and take advantage of that
wedge that currently exists between the
oligopoly of Verizon T-Mobile and uh and
AT&T. And honestly, I hate their guts. I
just installed Tesla solar panels and
the battery wall. I wired them their
money. Even though I was a little pissed
about one little thing I should make a
video on, but it's not worth being
pissed about this little thing. I am
just very picky. Okay. Okay. I'll I'll I
shouldn't [snorts] be doing this. You're
gonna get in trouble. Oh, I'll do it.
Okay. I love the Power Wall. Okay. I
have an NPhphase one at home with German
QC cell solar panels on the roof. I've
had them for like eight years. I'm a big
fan. Then I just got the Tesla ones. I
don't even know what the panels are.
They're probably the cheapest crap out
of China. Uh and uh and then the Tesla
Power Wall. But the YAP experience is
great. It's very polished. It's a great
product. They were really good at
installing. They're really good at
service. Like, they did a fantastic job.
I have no complaints for Tesla. Uh, with
the exception of one little thing, and
this is just me being a little pansy
douchebag. Okay, when you install panels
on a house,
I hate the lazy companies that do this,
and I understand why they do it. They
got to keep margins up, but I hate this.
The electrical panel, let's say, is
right here. Okay, I'm making it big so
you could see it. I know the electrical
panel isn't that big. Okay. And then
they run the conduit
from the battery and the disconnect to
the solar panels.
I want it to go through the roof.
But no, no, they got to take the conduit
and do this and then they're going to
paint it. And I'm like, that looks
Sorry, we can't flash your roof. Call a
roofer.
I'm too pissed for this today. So, I got
like 50,700
emails to get back to. Jeez, come on,
man. Like, the emails to the staff box
staff at Reinvest One for the people
upgrading to this. This is insane. Look
at this. It is 154. I got a million and
a half thousand things to do right now
and that's what I'm going to look
forward to in just a moment is help.
What is this?
Okay, so the point is the low band
acquisition is really smart by Elon and
SpaceX. They are smart people. They are
doing the right thing. This is the
future.
Uh, and it solves a lot of the bitching
that people have about it's never going
to work indoors. And then Elon goes,
Elon, I could just see him sitting like
on a throne with a beer and a gun. Or
honestly, I see him with like a whiskey
and a gun. Hold [music] my whiskey. And
then he goes and buys the 800 megahertz
spectrum, which gets you through the
walls. And then it's like, suck on these
nuts.
All right, I I can't handle this
anymore. Coupon expires tonight. Peace,
>> man. Your poor Kevin just lost lots of
money. Oh, but that's okay. [music]
I am with you. With you.
>> If you like that video, check this one
out. I think you're going to love it.
>> Why not advertise these things that you
told us here? I feel like nobody else
knows about this.
>> We'll we'll try a little advertising and
see how it goes. Congratulations, man.
You have done so much. People love you.
People look up to you.
>> Kevin Pra there, financial analyst and
YouTuber. Meet Kevin. Always great to
get your take.